Michael Bolton's Big, Sexy Valentine's Day Special is a
comedy, music film directed by Akiva Schaffer.
After Santa tells Michael Bolton that he needs 75,000 new babies by Christmas to meet toy
supply, he hosts a sexy telethon to get the world to start making love.
Self, played by Michael Bolton.
Adam Scott, played by Adam Scott.
Carmela, played by Sarah Shahi.
Ebenezer Scrooge, played by Matthew Kimbrough.
Misty, played by Sarah Silverman.
Punk rocker, played by Jorma Taccone.
Michael Bolton's Big, Sexy Valentine's Day Special is a Netflix variety
special starring Michael Bolton and created by The Lonely Island.
It was released on Netflix on February 7, 2017.
The film explores themes of celebrity, telethon,
valentine's day, sexy, celebrity host.
The tone is lighthearted.